<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="developed_by">Safe Season smart home technology Co.,Ltd \nNo.16, Independent street, Thuwanna Township, Yangon, Myanmar.
        \ncontact us: +95 (9) 776437645 \nemail: contactus@safeseasonmyanmar.com
    \nwww.safeseasonmyanmar.com</string>

    <string name="about_configuration">Smart Home server configuration Services (each a “Services” or “Configuration” and
        together the “Configuration Services”  or “Services”) are portfolio of services that include: hardware and software
        settings, operation system settings, floor configuration, clock configuration, etc.
    \nPlease Note: The Service Attachment to this Service Description include specification for each configuration Services detail in next other steps.</string>

    <string name="userResponsibilities">For each Configuration Service ordered by User hereunder, User shall</string>
    <string name="resp1">- Subject to these Terms, we grant you a non-exclusive, non-transferable (without a right to sub-licence) license to install and
        use the Reception App referred to in your Order during the applicable Subscription Term, in accordance with these Terms and the applicable Scope of Use.</string>
    <string name="resp2">- Subject to these Terms, we grant you a non-exclusive, non-transferable (without a right to sub-licence) license to install and use
        the Companion App during the applicable Subscription Term for the purpose of accessing and managing your use of the Reception App alongside the Management Portal.</string>
    <string name="resp3">- Unless otherwise specified in your Order, for each Site that you purchase, you may install one production instance of the Reception App
        on multiple Devices owned or operated by you (or your third party service providers so long as you remain responsible for their compliance with these Terms),
        provided that such Devices shall operate within the Site</string>

    <string name="warning">This will erase all configuration data and AI assistance log file form MCU, including:</string>
    <string name="warning_include">- Your registration data\n- Module registration data\n- Downloaded firmware database</string>
</resources>